얘네가 DDR중인 거처럼
Remember how we used to make these things look
낙서했던거 기억나?
like they were masturbating?
Brent Spiner, 뭐하는 짓이에요
Brent Spiner, what have you done?!
그건 Wesley Crusher 액션피겨
That was an original mint-in-package
풀패키지 진품이란 말입니다
Wesley Crusher action figure
내 친한 친구 윌 위튼이 싸인까지 한건데
signed by my close personal friend, Wil Wheaton.
미안해 멀대 같은 놈아
Sorry, Slim.
내 차 트렁크에 Mr.Data 인형있는데
I've got some Mr. Data dolls in the trunk of my car.
싸인해서 갖다 줄까?
You want me to sign one for you?
당신 이름 벌써 싸인됐거든요 Brent Spiner
You've already signed something, Brent Spiner.
내 리스트에 이름 싸인됐어요
Your name on my list.
지금 이 순간부터, 당신은 나의 적입니다
From this moment on, you are my mortal enemy.
걱정마세요 별거 아니에요
Don't worry. It doesn't take up a whole lot of your time.